Guide to the John W. Shenk Papers, 1900-1935
Department of Special Collections
John W. Shenk Papers,
1900-1935
Special Collections M0215
Shenk, John W., 1875-1959.
15.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of The Shenk Brothers, 1971.
Biographical Note
California Supreme Court Justice, 1924-1959. Involved in the development of water law in California.
Correspondence, printed material, photographs, and documents concerning Shenk's family, friends, family businesses (specialty chemical firm; land in the California Imperial Valley; and mining properties), and charitable, civic, and fraternal organizations. Justice Shenk's legal activities are represented to a minor degree.
Description:
The John W. Shenk Papers cover the period 1900 - 1935, with correspondence, printed matter, photographs, and documents principally concerning family, friends, family businesses (a specialty chemical firm; land in the Imperial Valley, California; mining properties), and charitible, civic and fraternal organizations. Justice Shenk's legal activities are represented to a minor degree.
All correspondence is arranged in alphabetical order by sender. Unless otherwise indicated, all letters are to Justice Shenk. Letters from Justice Shenk are listed under his name, pages 27 - 51.
Folder titles are indicated by capital letters. The earliest and latest correspondence from each sender is indicated by the numbers in the right hand column.
A - GENERAL FILE. 1 - 2
Abbott, William M. '30
Acacia Club. '22-'23(4)
AMERICAN LAW INSTITUTE. '26-'31(10) 1 - 3
Ames, E. Neal. '30(2)
In the above sample listing, there are two folders mentioned. One, folder 1 - 2 (folder two in box 1) contains the general file for the letter A. In it are letters from Mr. Abbott, the Acacia Club, and Mr. Ames, among others. From Mr. Abbott, there is one letter, dated 1930. From the Acacia Club, four letters dated 1922 or 1923.
In a separate folder, there are ten letters from the American Law Institute, the earliest of which is dated 1926, the latest, 1931. This is box one, folder three.
Throughout the list, Justice Shenk will be abbreviated as JWS.
Container List
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - UNIDENTIFIED., (15) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A - GENERAL FILE. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abbott, William M. (1872-)., '30
    - Abel, Edson C., '22
    - Acacia Club., '22-'23; (4)
    - Acunta, L. D., '20
    - Adams, Ida May., nd, '23-'26; (3)
    - Addleman, Joseph A., '33-'35; (9)
    - Aetna Life Insurance Company., '30-'31
    - Aggeler, William Tell (1866 -)., '19-'34; (4)
    - Agnew, H. M., '26
    - Ainslie, Frederick G., '33
    - Aitken & Aitken., '30
    - Alameda County Bar Association.
      See BAR ASSOCIATIONS.
    - Alberti, Robert A., '24
    - Alderson, William A., '31-'32
    - Alexander, Charles (1897 -)., '14
    - Alexander, Jewel., '35
    - Alhambra District Bar Association.
    - Allan, Robert N., '20
    - Allen & Co., '24
    - Allen, Alfred W., '31-'34
    - Allen, Carroll., '25-'31; (3)
    - Allen, William., '26-'34
    - Allin, Ernest., '20; (2)
    - Al Malaikah Temple (A.A.O.N.M.S.)., nd, '20-'26; (7)
    - Amador Valley Savings Bank., '28-'32
    - American Bar Association., '26
      See also BAR ASSOCIATIONS.
    - American Committee For Devastated France., '23
    - American Electric Railway Association., '30
    - American Historical Society., '20-'23
    - American Judicature Society., '33
    - American Law Book Company., '24; (3)
    - AMERICAN LAW INSTITUTE., '26-'31; (10) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Legion., nd, '19-'34; (6)
    - American Voters Association., '28
    - Ames, E. Neal., '30; (2)
    - Anderson, C. Sherman., '29
    - Anderson, Hugh S. (1890 -)., '24
    - Anderson, James., '24
    - Anderson, Lively Lee., '24
    - Anderson, S. W., '24
    - Anderson, William H., '24-'33; (8)
    - Andreani, Frank M., '22-'31; (3)
    - Andrews, Alexander B., '26-'28
    - Angell, H. J., '14
    - Angellotti, Frank M. (1861 -)., '18-'27; (3)
    - ANONA GOLD MINING AND MILLING COMPANY., '03-'29; (183) (Box 1, Folder 4, Folder 5)
      --Documents, legal papers, receipts, lists, notices.
    - Anti Street Light Maintenance Association., nd
    - Army and Navy Prescott Club.
    - Arnold, Grace., `28
    - Arnold, Ralph., `26
    - Ashburn, Allen W., `24
    - Associated Realty Boards Of California., `10
    - Atherton, A. W., nd; (2)
    - Ault & Anderson., `24
    - Austin, Robert E., `27
    - Automobile Club Of Southern California., nd, `20-`25; (10)
    - Avery, Russ., `24
    - Aviado, Joseph., `23
    - Ayres, Albert D., `29; (2)
  - B - GENERAL FILE. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Baba, Malcolm., `22
    - Babson Institute., `32
    - Bailey, A. G., `30
    - Bailey, J. M.
      See ANONA GOLD MINING AND MILLING CO.
    - Bailie, Norman A., `26-`30
    - Baird, William S. (1877 -)., `27-`28
    - Baker, Arthur., `25
    - Bancroft-Whitney Company., `24-`32; (3)
    - BANK OF AMERICA., `24-`34; (40) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bantzer, Edward H., `20
    - BAR ASSOCIATIONS., `19-`35; (83) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Barden, Harold E., `24
    - Barker, Donald., `07
    - Barker, George H., `24
    - Barker Brothers., `23-`24
    - Barnes, C. Rankin., `24
    - Barnes, Frank T. (1891 -)., `28-`29; (3)
    - Barnett, Ray E., `20
    - Barnhill, William A., `24
    - Barrett, R. M., `30
    - Barry, P. H., `15
    - Barry, R. W., `24
    - Barry, W. H., `32
    - Bartoo, Mrs. E., `24
    - Bassett, Wilbur., `27; (2)
    - Baum, Willis M., `30
    - Baumann, Henry., `08
    - Baxter, William., nd, `23; (2)
    - Baze, Ross B., `25
    - Beal, Mrs. Bessie R., `22
      See also OHIO WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY.
    - Beaman, Alexander Gaylord (1885 -)., `22-`25; (3)
    - Beardsley, John., `14
    - Bearman, William W., `20-`23; (3)
    - Beaumont, Campbell E., `35
    - Becker, ---., `22
    - Becker, Tracy Chatfield., `31-`34; (5)
    - Beebe, George., `31
    - Beek, Joseph A. (1888 -)., `23
    - Beirne, William B., `31
    - Bell, Hobart.
      See OHIO WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY.
    - Bell, Robson O.
    - Bell Chesterfield Bed Company., '30
    - Benedict, H. Stanley., '13-'24
    - Benjamin, M. J., '26-'29
    - Bennett, Mrs. Earl D., '32-'33; (8)
    - Bennett, Edmon Gordon., '14
    - Bennett, James S., '14; (2)
    - Bent, Charles E., nd, '25-'35; (7)
    - Bergquist, Carl J., '30
    - Berkebile, Thomas A., '23-'25
    - Bernstein, D. Brandon., '34; (2)
    - Berry, Frederick L., '28
    - BETA THETA PI., '20-'35; (19) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Betkouski, Martin F., '27
    - Bettencourt, Joseph., '24-'29; (24)
    - Better America Federation of California., '31
    - Better Homes and Gardens., '31
    - Bill, G. D., '20
    - Billig, Clint A., '00-'35; (3)
    - Birdsell, Ray E., '22
    - George J. Birkel Company., '22
    - Bishop, Edward T., '25-'35
    - Bitler, Don C., '24
    - Blackburn, Porter C., '26; (2)
    - Blair, Isidor D., '31
    - Blair, John L., '26
    - Blakeley, H. B., '26-'31
    - Blanchard, H. A., '26
    - Blanks, A. F., '24-'25; (9)
    - Bledsoe, Benjamin F. (1874 -)., '27
    - Blight, Reynold E. (1879 -)., '24-'26; (5)
    - Bliss, Charles H. J., '23
    - Blood, Florence Porter., '14
    - Bockmon, W. E., '24
    - Bollier, Paul E., '26
    - Bolo Club Of Los Angeles California., nd, '13-'17; (7)
    - Bonham Brothers., '29
    - Boone, Thomas C., '33
    - Bordwell, Matthews & Wadsworth., '32
    - Borden, Sheldon., '24
    - Boswell, Harry J., '13
    - Bowen, William Alvin (1877 -)., '10
    - Bowers, Walter L. (1883 -)., '35; (2)
    - Bowman, Marie E., nd
    - Boynton, Albert E., '27-'29
    - Boys, Howard M., '27
    - Boys' Day In Citizenship., '34
    - Braden, Grover J., '25
    - Bradford, Kimball & Company., '30
    - Brain, R. T., '18
    - Breakfast Club., '26
    - Breslin, George M., '24
    - Brick, Alexander., '21
    - Briggs, Anna B., '20
    - Brock, William E., '25-'26; (4)
    - Brooks, Leon D., '26
    - Brooks, R. A., '13
    - Brown, Luther G., '23-'26; (6)
    - Brown, Thomas P., '34
    - Brown, William H., '14
    - Browne Roof Company., '28; (2)
    - Brownell, Herbert J. (1904 -)., '26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Brownstein, Dan J., '23
    - BRYAN, WILLIAM JENNINGS (1860 - 1925)., '15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Bryant, W. Byron., '35; (2)
    - Bryce, W. G., '20
    - Bryson, Charles W., '24
    - Budd, Claya A., '29
    - Buehler, Harold M., '27-'28
    - Bullock, Georgia P., '31; (2)
    - Bundy, Carl A., '22
    - Burch, Ann., '26
    - Buren, Frank., '31
    - Burke, John C., '33
    - Burke, John P. (1862 -)., '24
    - Burke, W. Maxwell., '24-'26; (4)
    - Burkhardt, Willem Neil (1889 -)., '30
    - Burnett, C. H., '27
    - Burr, Ed A., nd
    - Burton, John F., '25
    - Bush, George C., '24
    - Bush, Samuel T., '26-'27; (3)
    - Business Men's Protective Association., '17
    - Business Stability Association., '14
    - Business Women's Civic Club., '14
    - Butcher, Carr Harbison., '27; (2)
    - Butterworth, E. S., '14
    - Byekett, --- Agnes., nd
    - Byrnes, Harold J., '34; (2)
    - Byrnes, John L., '31
  - C - GENERAL FILE. (I) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Cabaniss, George H. Jr., '31; (2)
    - Calexico National Bank., '11
    - California, State Of.
      - Blue Book., '28
      - Board Of Control., '27
      - Board Of Prison Directors., '30
      - Corporation Department., '22
      - Crime Commission., '27; (2)
      - Department Of Public Works., '32; (2)
      - Prison At San Quentin., '22-'30; (5)
      - Supreme Court., '29; (2)
      - University. Boalt Hall., '31-'32
    - California Federation Of Women's Clubs., '31
    - California Independent., '20
    - California Joint Immigration Committee., '30
    - California League., '20
    - California Men Of Prominence, Ltd., nd, '32; (2)
    - California Real Estate Association., '24
    - California State Bar Association.
    - California Taxpayers' Association., '26
    - Cameron, Florence, '46
    - Cammert, E. R., '28
    - Campaign Committee For Power Bonds., '13
    - Campbell, Ira Alexander (1878 -)., nd, '11; (3)
    - Campbell, Kemper B., '14-'29; (4)
    - Campbell, Litta Belle (Mrs. Kemper)., nd, '29-'32; (7)
    - [Campbell, Louis G.], nd
    - [Cannon, James Jr. (1864 -).], '34
    - Carey, John G., '24
    - Carlin, Keith., '27
    - Carlson, Arthur J., '26
    - Carlson, Milton., '14
    - Carleton, Frank E., '32; (2)
    - Carns, Charles Newell (1885 -)., nd
    - Carpenter, Walter C., '23
    - Carr, P.E., '16
    - Carr, Sterling Douglas (1876 -)., '35
    - Carr, William J., '20
    - Carroll, Maynard C., nd
    - Carter, Henry E., '27
    - CARTER, JESSE W. (1888 -)., 24-'35; (12) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Carter, Martin G., '24-'31
    - Cary, W. P., '22-'24
    - Casie, C.D., '23
    - Castle, J. Jay., '33
    - Catholic Laymen's Retreat Association., '29; (2)
    - [Catlin, Franklin S.], '10
    - Cerf, Marcel E., '35
    - Chaffee, Adna R., '11; (2)
    - CHAMBERLIN, HARRY., '24-'30; (13) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Champ, Charles C., '22; (2)
    - Champ, Mrs. Charles C., '22; (2)
    - The Champion., '14
    - Chandler, Charles L.
    - Chandler, Harry (1864 -)., nd, '24-'34; (4)
    - Chaplain Alfred S. Clark Camp No. 56., '14
    - Chase, C. Franklin., '23
    - Chase, Ralph A., '13
    - Chenoweth, Orr M., '30; (2)
    - Cheroske, Sebald L., '31
    - Cherrington, Charles E., '20
    - Chipman, Ida E., '24
    - Chisam, C. J., '24
    - Christensen, Harry N., '25
    - Church, Percy Clarke., '26
    - Citizens' Committee For Reception To Captain Carl Spindler., '31
    - City Club Of Los Angeles., '14
  - C - GENERAL FILE. (II) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Clark, J. B., '23; (3)
    - Clarke, Lucian J., '31; (4)
    - Clarke, Robert M., '29-'33; (3)
    - Clarke, Thurmond., '29-'32; (3)
    - Clarkson, James H. B., '22-'23; (3)
    - Cleary, Alfred J., '32; (2)
    - Clock, Ralph H., nd, '28
    - Cluss, William R., '13
    - Cockrell, Ewing., '28
    - Coffin, Chester L., '27
    - Cohen, Ben C., '26; (2)
    - Coil, Ernest B., '14
    - Cokely, Mrs. W. H., nd
    - Cole, Louis Maurice (1870 -)., '22-'25; (4)
    - Cole, Mrs. O. P., '24
    - Coleman, B. H., '25
    - Coles, Joseph D. (1887 -)., '24
    - COLLIER, FRANK C. ()., nd, '14-'32; (30) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Collings, Lewis D., nd, '26-'31
    - Collins, Holdridge Ozro., '26
    - Comegys, Lloyd C., '27
    - Committee Of 100., '14
    - Committee On Masonic Education., '26
    - Commonwealth Club Of California., '25-'33; (6)
    - Commonwealth Trust Company., nd
    - Conkling, F. L., '14 - '22
    - Conlee, Monroe H., '33; (2)
    - Conley, William Maxwell (1866 -)., '17
    - Connerly, F. T., '26
    - Connor, J. P., '23 - '27
    - CONREY, NATHANIEL P., '23-'32; (13) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Contra Costa County., nd
    - Converse, Charles., '24
    - Cook, W. J., '23
    - Cooper, Bert L., '23
    - Cooper, Carl V., '32
    - Cooper, John S., '27
    - Copp, Andrew J. Jr., '23-'31; (3)
    - Corbell, Louis M., '27
    - Corbett, Howard W., '25
    - Cornish, Frank V., '28
    - Corten, Everett A., '34
    - Couch, J. P., '23
    - Coultas, G. W., '14
    - Council, C. B., '30
    - Council, Lucile., nd
    - Council, William H., '24-'33; (6)
    - The Courier., '14
    - Coutts, John M., '30
    - Cowell, A. F., '23
    - Craft, Kenneth S., '22
    - Craig, Elliot., '29
    - Craig, Gavin W., '22
    - Craig, J. C., '24
    - Craig, William T., '27
    - Crail, Charles S., '23-'34; (14)
    - Crane, A. Bathurst., '25
    - Crane-Gartz, Kate., '23
    - Cranford, J. H., '25; (2)
    - Cranston, William., '33
    - Crawford, Jack., '31
    - Crawford, Samuel J., '20-'30
    - Creamer, Michael., '24
    - Cremin, J. M., '25
    - Crescent Bay Waiters Club., '14
    - Cressaty, B., '06
    - Cressey, F. G., '14; (2)
    - Crippen, Paul A., '14; (3)
    - Crocker, William Harry (1861 -)., '31
    - Crouch, Charles C., '33; (3)
    - Crowell, W. Hall., '30-'31; (4)
    - Crown Transfer and Storage Company., '24-'25
    - Crownover, John N., '30; (2)
    - CRUMP, GUY RICHARDS., '24-'35; (14) (Box 2, Folder 11)
      See also IRELAND, IN RE ESTATE OF.
    - Cruzan, Harold Ide., '31
    - Cryer, George Edward (1875 -)., '11-'23
    - Culver, J. W., '24
    - Culver, Richard J. O., nd, '24-'32; (8)
    - Cumming, Joseph M., '24
    - Curet, Adrien., '34
    - Curtin, John T., '22-'26; (7)
    - Curtis, Jesse W., '24-'25
    - Custer, Charles R., '24-'28
  - D - GENERAL FILE. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Daily News Of San Francisco., nd, '30
    - Daly, John E., '14
    - Dam, F. H., '33
    - Daney, Eugene., '30
    - Daniels, Earle M., '24
    - Danielson, Carl A., '23
    - Daugherty, Edwin M., '34
    - DAUGHERTY, HARRY MUAJAH (1860 -)., '24; (3) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Daughters Of the American Revolution., '31-'34; (17)
    - Davidson, Bert T., '34; (2)
    - Davis, Moses C., '24
    - Dawson, John D., '20
    - Deckman, Martha., '24
    - DeCrescenzo, Letitia., nd
    - DeGarmo, B. W., '32
    - DeGarmo, G. C.
    - Delapp, W. H., '08-'27
    - Dell, Sidney., '11; (20)
    - Delta Chi. Los Angeles Alumni Chapter., '15
    - Delta Theta Phi., nd, '30
    - Dennett, L. L., '27
    - DeSantis, A. S., '24
    - Desmond, Walter J., '22-'34
    - Devenir, Lois Marie., nd
    - Dickinson, W. R., '20
    - Dillon, Richard J., '11-'24
    - Dinkelspiel, Henry G. W., nd
    - Dishman, Edward T., '13
    - Docker, Frederick W., '29
    - Dodge, Jonathan S., '20-'32; (7)
    - Dodge, Miles., '29-'31; (5)
    - Dodson, George Rowland (1865 -)., '20-'25
    - Dodson, Philip F., '24-'35; (4)
    - Dole, E. J., '27
    - Donohugh, W. L., '19-'20; (6)
    - Doody, Leo., '34
    - Doran, William C., '24-'34
    - Dorrington, J. W.
    - Dorton, James W., '22
    - Dosh, R. H.
    - Doty, F. E., '22
    - Dougherty, P. B., '25
    - Dove, F. Roy., '23-'25; (6)
    - Dove, T. C., '27
    - Down Town Association Of San Francisco., '34
    - Drake, Mr. and Mrs.
    - Drake, Marjory H., '27; (2)
    - Dreifus, Charles., '24
    - Dryer, George W. (1881 -)., '24
    - Duniway, Ben C., '31
    - Dunker, Minnie E., '31
    - Dunlavy, Melvin T., '31
    - Duvall, Trumbull Gillette (1861 -)., '31
    - Dwiggins, E., '22
    - Dyar, Frederick R., '20-'24
    - Dyke, Harry N., '32
  - E - GENERAL FILE. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - East Gate Chapter No. 103, R.A.M., '20
    - East Side Political Club of Los Angeles., '14; (2)
    - East Side Republican Club., '30
    - Easton, William E., '24-'27; (4)
    - Eaton, Fred., nd, '27
    - Eddy, Cora B., '25
    - Eddy, Elford., '24
    - Ediphone., '28
    - Edmonds, Douglas L., '23-'35; (8)
    - Edwards, David W., '22
    - Edwards, H. R., '34
    - Edwards, LeRoy M., '23
    - Edwards-Hostetler Studio., '23; (2)
    - Ehnes, Morris Wellington (1873 -)., '24
    - Ehrhorn, Sue Springer., '07
    - El Camino Golf and Country Club., '35
    - Elder, T. M.
    - Eldridge, Frederick William (1877 -)., '22
    - S. T. Eldridge Campaign Committee., '14
    - Elijah, M. C., '22-'23
    - ELKS, BENEVOLENT PROTECTIVE ORDER OF., nd, '14-'34; (20) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Elliott, Emma., '22
    - Elliott, John B., '24
    - Elwell, J. F., '35
    - Emerson, Richard S., '25; (2)
    - Emme, Otto J., '23; (2)
    - Emmons, C. H., '24
    - The Emporium., '28
    - Encell, Harry A. (1880 -)., '32
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica., '28
    - English, Frank Clare (1869 -)., '33
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the U.S., '23-'26; (9)
    - The John M. Eshleman Memorial Association., '29
    - Esterly, Will., '24
    - Eubank, C. H., '20
    - Eureka Refining Co., '27
    - Evans, Perry., '27
    - Eversole, Keith C., nd, '24-'32; (11)
    - Eyton, Charles., '20
  - F - GENERAL FILE. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Faries, David R. (1891 -)., '23-'25; (3)
    - Farrand, George E., '31
    - Faulkner, Al. G., '31
    - Faulkner, J. Burton., '23
    - Federal Land Bank Of Berkeley., '25; (2)
    - Feemster & Cleary., '27
    - Ferguson, Milton James (1879 -)., '20
    - Fidelity Savings and Loan Association., '23; (2)
    - Fifth Avenue Library Society., '07-'08
    - Finch, William M., '30; (2)
    - FINLAYSON, FRANCIS G., '23-'27; (10) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - First Methodist Episcopal Church., '19
    - First National Bank of Los Angeles.
      See SECURITY FIRST NATIONAL BANK OF LOS ANGELES.
    - Fischer, Will H., nd
    - Fitch, H. G., '24
    - A. E. Fitkin & Co., '26
    - Fitts, Buron., '26
    - Fitzgerald, Fred J., '24-'25
    - Fitzgerald, Robert Mullins (1858 -)., '26
    - Flaherty, Anna B., '23-'24
    - Fleming, E. J., '10
    - Fleming, John L., '29-'31; (4)
    - Fletcher, Kimball., '22-'28; (3)
    - Flint, Motley H. (1865 -)., '08-'11; (5)
    - Flowerman, J. N., '33
    - Flowers For Congress Club., nd
    - Flynn, John L., '25
    - Foote, D. A., '24
    - Ford, W. Joseph., '31
    - Foreign Service., '25
    - Foreman & Clark., '22
    - Forest Lawn Memorial Park., '22-'31; (6)
    - Forrester, C. Henry., '23; (2)
    - Foster, Laura., '25
    - Fourth Ohio Voluntary Infantry Association., '25
    - Fox, W. Turney., '31-'32; (3)
    - Fox, Willard Henry., '14
    - Frankum, Anna M., '24
    - Fraternal Order Of Eagles., '20
    - Frazer, Guernsey., '25
    - Frazier, Henry A., '20-'22; (4)
    - Fredericks, John Donovan (1867 -)., '23-'24
    - Fredin, E. P., '26
    - Freeman, George R., '30
    - Freitas, Carlos R., '30
    - Fricke, Charles W., '27-'34
    - Friedlander, J. M., '26-'29
    - Fritts, Edna., '24
    - Frontier Asthma Co., '20-'22
    - Fulcher, Charles E. R., '24-'30; (5)
    - Fuld, Stanley H., '25
    - Fuller, G. H., '24
    - Fulton & Fulton., '29
  - G - GENERAL FILE. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Galen, Albert J., '25
    - Galley, Elizabeth., '24
    - Gammon, James M., '31
    - Gant, Valentine., '06-'08; (3)
    - Gardner, Oliver Max (1882 -)., '20
    - Garland, William May (1866 -)., '22; (2)
    - Garrison., '13
    - Garrison, Walter E., '32
    - Geer, Margaret., '27
    - Geer, Richard L., '34
    - General Defense Committee., '23
    - George, A., '22
    - Gerecht, E. F., '23
    - Gerlack, Alvin., '26
    - German American League., '14
    - Germania., '14
    - Gibbs, G. A., '20-'24; (4)
    - Gibbs, William W. Jr., '24
    - Gibson-Heston-Guertin., '23
    - Gibson, Lilburn., '27; (3)
    - Gibson, William A., '23-'24
    - Gifford, Harry N., nd, '08-'30; (9)
    - Gilbreath, J. W., '13
    - Glendale Bar Association.
    - Glide Memorial Methodist Episcopal Church., '31
    - Globe Petroleum Corporation., nd, '22-'25; (8)
    - Glover, George A., '26; (2)
    - Godfrey, Marcus L., '29
    - Godfrey, Marcus L. Jr., '33
    - Goff, Roy., '24
    - Goldschmidt, Hermann H., nd, '31; (6)
    - Goodcell, Rex B., '31
    - Goodell, C. J., '27-'29
    - Goodman, Louis E., '31
    - Goodrich, Herbert F. (1889 -).
      See AMERICAN LAW INSTITUTE.
    - Gordon, George Breed (1860 - 1927)., '22
    - Gordon, Hugh., '25
    - Goree, L. J. Jr., '30
    - Gottesfeld, Harry., '26
    - Gould, Thomas C., '24-'34; (3)
    - Gould, Will D., '24
    - Graham, Harry., '27-'30; (3)
    - Graney, Donald C., '33; (2)
    - Granville, Sylvia M., '22
    - Graves, J. A., '25
    - Graves, M. O., '14; (2)
    - Gray, C., '23
    - Gray, J. Walter., '28
    - Gray, Louisa M., nd
    - Graydon, Betty Marshall., '31
    - Greater Los Angeles., nd; (2)
    - Green, Dan W., '30-'35; (3)
    - Green, Donald R., '22
    - Green, Mabel R., '22
    - Greene, Hilda E., '30; (2)
    - Greenstock, Minnie A. Symondson., '24-'31; (6)
    - Greenwald, A., '20
    - Gregory, Miles S., nd, '20; (3)
    - James B. Gresham Post No. 8, V.F.W., '20; (2)
    - Griffith, Jones, and John J. Craig., '22
    - Grinnell, Frank W., '26
    - Griswold, H. H. Inc., '25
    - Griswold, Edward., '32
    - Grolier Society., nd
    - Grua, Edward T., '27
    - Guerin, C. W., '24; (2)
    - Guernsey, Louis G., '21-'24
    - Guernsey, P. B., '30
    - Guiler, Henry Anderson., '27
    - Guthery, E. G., '20-'25
  - H - GENERAL FILE. (I) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Haas, Charles E. (1873 -)., '15-'31; (9)
    - Haas, Walter F., '35
    - Haase, Ethel L., '24
    - Haber, Michael., '28
    - Hagerty, Charles J., '30
    - Haggerty, William A.
    - Hahn And Hahn., '14-'26
    - Hahn, S. S., '20-'29
    - Hall, Asa., '24
    - Hall, Hubert E., '25
    - Hall, Wilbur., nd, '13
    - Hallman, Mario H., '27
    - Hamilton, Mrs. G. A., '06
    - Hamilton, William B., '31
    - Hammer, Fred. H., nd
    - Hammon, Percy V., '23
    - Haneman Realty Co., '13
    - Hanley, Robert L., '24-'27; (3)
    - Hanlon, William J., '31-'33
    - Hanna, Byron C. (1887 -)., '27; (2)
    - Hanna, Sam C., '32
    - Hannon, E., nd
    - Hannon, J. Vincent., '26
    - Harper, J. C., '30
    - Harris, E. B., '20
    - Harris, George B., '23-'35; (6)
    - Harris, Kirk., '29
    - Harris, Lamar A., '07
    - Harris, Nick B., '27
    - Harrold, Frank E., '07
    - Hartman, L. O., '29
    - Hartsook Studio., '22
    - Hartung, Hugh K., nd
    - Harvey, John G., nd
    - Hastings, Hill., nd
    - Hatfield, George J. (1887 -)., '35
    - Hatheway, David Gilbert., '27
    - Hatteroth, W. H., '26
    - Haverty, Thomas., '20-'24
    - Hawkins, J. W., '24
    - Hazard, Leonard., '13
    - Hazlett, William., '23-'28; (4)
    - Heales, Earl LeRoy., nd; (2)
    - Heaney, Price & Postel., '32
    - Heath, Harvey L., '23
    - Heath, J. E., nd
    - Heffley, George R., '24
    - Held, William D. L., '30
    - Held, William Jr., '30
    - Hellman, Marco H. (1878 -)., '27
    - Hellman Bank., '22-'23
    - Helms, Elmer Ellsworth (1863 -)., '21
    - Helser, Charles W., '25
    - Hencroach, Charles., '24
    - Henderson's., '13
    - Henderson, Frank G., '13-'29
    - Henderson, George A., '25-'26; (3)